Johnny Otis Collection, 1949-2012 SC 106
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 4. Radio Airchecks, Johnny Otis Show
  - 4.2. KPFK (Los Angeles) and KPFA (Berkeley), 1982-1994
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1987?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2625
      contents unknown
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Roy Milton Tribute, 1987?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2626
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r76f06nx3v
      Brief show segment featuring the music of Roy Milton including "Milton's Boogie," "Red Light" (featuring Johnny Otis) and "Best Wishes."
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1987?; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Robert McKnight
      EC10 2627; EC10 2628; EC10 2629
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Ruth Brown, Cadets, B.B. King, Four Tops, Brook Benton & Dinah Washington, Coasters, Little Milton, Fontella Bass, Ramsey Lewis, John Lee Hooker, Little Richard, Etta James, Lightnin' Hopkins, Elmore James, and Lloyd Price. Otis talks with friends.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Lloyd Price, John Lee Hooker, The Drifters, Jimmy Reed, Jimmy McCracklin, Koko Taylor, Fats Waller, Aretha Franklin, Dorothy Love Coates & The Gospel Harmonettes, Billie Holiday, and Stevie Wonder. Otis talks to McKnight about his motivational workshops, followed by comedy segment.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of John Lee Hooker, Fats Domino, Dizzy Gillespie, Miriam Makeba, Richard Berry & The Dreamers, Jay McShann featuring Walter Brown, Lionel Hampton, Big Mama Thornton, Charles Brown, Muddy Waters, Jimmie Lunceford, Art Tatum, Mary Lou Williams, Shuggie Otis, Coasters, and The Five Keys. Comedy segment followed by Otis promo for the Landmark Church's food drive for the homeless.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: KPFK Fundraiser, 1987?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2652
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t74c683h88
      Otis plays the music of Larry Williams, Little Willie John, Little Junior Parker, Bobby Bland, Joe Turner, Jackie Wilson, Dinah Washington, B.B. King, and Elmore James. Otis asks for donations for the KPFK fund drive.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: KPFK Fundraiser, 1987?; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Shelly Rim, John Patton Jr., Ken McNight
      EC10 2683; EC10 2684
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v23v83fm3s
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Professor Longhair, Jessie Hill, Ernie K-Doe, Dr. John, Lee Dorsey, Huey "Piano" Smith, Cadets, Ben E. King, Billie Holiday, Champion Jack Dupree, Johnnie Taylor, Clifton Chenier, Joe Tex, Fats Domino, Chick Webb featuring Ella Fitzgerald, Count Basie featuring Jimmy Rushing, and The Drifters. Otis solicits donations for KPFK.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of The Clovers, Ray Charles, Lightnin' Hopkins, Lee Allen, Barbara George, Louis Armstrong, Duke Ellington, Otis Redding, Aretha Franklin, Perez Prado, Clarence Henry, Mahalia Jackson, Coasters, and Four Tops. Otis and Ken McNight talk about the Landmark Church's food drive for the homeless. Otis promotes an upcoming gig and solicits donations for KPFK. Otis and John Patton Jr. talk about his role in the movie "The Color Purple," then Otis talks with jazz drummer Shelly Rim.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1987?; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tom McElhaney
      EC10 3684; EC10 3685
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Big Joe Turner, Wilbert Harrison, Teen Queens, Duke Ellington, Billy Ward & The Dominoes, B.B. King, Gladys Knight & The Pips, Billie Holiday, Stevie Wonder, and Koko Taylor. Otis and friends talk about an upcoming music festival in Oakland, Otis's upcoming art book, and cartoons that Otis is making as decorations for his new deli/nightclub.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Lowell Fulson, Johnny Otis, Brenda Boykin, Ray Charles, LaVern Baker, Muddy Waters, Duke Ellington, Johnny Tolbert, and The Shirelles. Otis and friends talk about upcoming Oakland music festival. Otis talks to Tom McElhaney about his Top 500 list and Otis talks about his dog, Pookie.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live from the Fairmont Hotel in San Jose, 1988-01-02; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Bob Frazier, Tom McElhaney, Curtis Jay
      EC10 2632; EC10 2633
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t945747d3h
      Tape 1: Opens with the conclusion of Emmit Powell's gospel radio show, then segues into the Johnny Otis Show. Otis plays the music of Stevie Wonder, Shirley & Lee, Ike and Tina Turner, Mary Wells, Brenton Wood, Monotones, Coasters, Little Richard, Katie Webster, Wilson Pickett, Little Walter, Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson, Chuck Willis, T-Bone Walker, 5 Royales, Muddy Waters and Sly Stone. Otis and Bob Frazier talk about Ike and Tina Turner's early band, promote Denise LaSalle show in Berkeley. Otis talks to other guests including deejay Curtis Jay (KFJC: Santa Clara).
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Sly Stone, Little Milton, Supremes, Dinah Washington, Big Mama Thornton, Joe Turner, Art Tatum, Sarah Vaughan, Ella Fitzgerald, B.B. King, Lightnin' Hopkins, Staple Singers, Billie Holiday, and Sam Taylor. Otis and guests talk about Sly Stone, Dinah Washington, Art Tatum, and compare blues artists.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live from the Fairmont Hotel in San Jose, 1988-01?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Bob Frazier, Tom McElhaney
      EC10 2634
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r66j03kv83
      Opens with the conclusion of Emmit Powell's gospel radio show, then segues into the Johnny Otis Show. Otis plays the music of Lloyd Price, Ray Sharp, Jimmy McCracklin, Fats Waller, BB King, Ernie K-Doe, Memphis Minnie, Esther Phillips, Etta James, Gene & Eunice, Muddy Waters, Count Basie, and Ray Charles. Otis talks with guests and audience members, tells stories about Fats Waller, and more.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live from the Fairmont Hotel in San Jose, 1988-01?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tom McElhaney, George Hood
      EC10 2640
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v53j92pc3g
      Otis plays the music of Joe Turner, Marvin Gaye, Duke Ellington, and Tiny Bradshaw. Otis talks with George Hood, a nutritionist, in the lobby of the Fairmont Hotel.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1988-01?; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Tom McElhaney, Bob Frazier
      EC10 2641
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s55m317n9k
      Otis plays the music of Jimmy Reed, Drifters, Etta James, Martha and the Vandellas, Platters, Jackie Wilson, Ernie K-Doe, Fats Domino, Fats Waller, Teen Queens, Junior Walker, Johnny Otis, and Elmore James. Otis talks with guests in between records.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1988-01-09; 4 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Shuggie Otis, Jackie Payne, Nicky Otis, Bob Frazier
      EC10 2447; EC10 2448; EC10 2449; EC10 2450
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/386019zc5n
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Hank Ballard & The Midnighters, Four Tops, Sam & Dave, Louis Jordan, Stevie Wonder, Fats Waller, Martha & The Vandellas, Junior Walker, B.B. King, Jimmie Lunceford, Count Basie, Aretha Franklin, and Koko Taylor. Otis promotes upcoming Junior Walker concert.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of The Dubs, Turbans, Lowell Fulson, Jimmy Reed, Soul Stirrers, Billie Holiday, Johnny Otis & Shuggie Otis, Fats Domino, Chuck Willis, Duke Ellington, Marvin Gaye, and Mickey & Sylvia. Live performance by Shuggie, Jackie Payne, Nicky, and Johnny. Otis and friends talk about Mickey & Sylvia, Don & Dewey, and upcoming concerts.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of LaVern Baker, Brook Benton, Little Milton, Frankie Lymon, Don & Dewey, Sam & Dave, El Dorados, Drifters, Dinah Washington, Little Richard, Big Mama Thornton, Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson, and Dominoes, followed by comedy segment.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Mickey & Sylvia.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live from the Fairmont Hotel in San Jose, 1988-01-16; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Bob Frazier, Tom McElhaney
      EC10 2451; EC10 2452
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p09623qh6g
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Elmore James, Martha & The Vandellas, Richard Berry, Jesse Belvin, Mary Wells, Sam Cooke, Jimmie Lunceford, Dinah Washington, Preston Love & Shuggie Otis, Shirelles, Lightnin' Hopkins, Count Basie, Professor Longhair, Teen Queens, Amos Milburn, and Clyde McPhatter.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Little Milton, Hank Ballard, T-Bone Walker, Louis Jordan, Bobby Lewis, Bo Diddley, Big Joe Turner, Muddy Waters, Lester Young, Junior Parker, Tommy Tucker, Bobby "Blue" Bland, Staple Singers, Harmonizing Four, and Billie Holiday. Otis and friends chat about the Fairmont Hotel.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Lloyd Price Tribute, 1988-01-30; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Bob Frazier
      EC10 2453; EC10 2454
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n89d17k28j
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Otis Redding & Carla Thomas, Roy Milton, Sam & Dave, Supremes, Lloyd Price, Miriam Makeba, Sam Cooke & The Soul Stirrers, Billie Holiday, Little Richard, B.B. King, Marvelettes, Jimmy Reed, Little Junior Parker, and Drifters. Otis talks about clothing styles when he started out.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Nina Simone, Bo Diddley, Lloyd Price, Big Joe Turner, Jackie Wilson, Elmore James, Bessie Smith, Ben Webster, Barret Strong, T-Bone Walker, Charles Brown, Shirley & Lee, and Spaniels. Otis and friends talk about "One O'Clock Jump" and their Top 10 Blues Songs list.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Eddie Vinson Memorial, 1988-07; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.
      EC10 2330
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v93504z97q
      Otis plays the music of Memphis Slim, Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson, Ray Charles, Coasters, Sam Cooke, Johnny & Shuggie Otis with Delmar Evans, Clifton Chenier, Sam & Dave, Tampa Red, and the Marvelettes. Otis talks about the life and career of Eddie Vinson.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live from the Paramount Hotel, New Orleans, 1988-08-22; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): John DeMers
      EC10 2455; EC10 2456; EC10 2457
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/217q67r09b
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, Wilson Pickett, Bobby Bland, Ray Charles, Barbara George, Count Basie, Fats Domino, Lightnin' Hopkins, Professor Longhair, Chuck Berry, Little Willie John, Ikettes, Louis Armstrong, and Johnny Otis.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Mercy Dee, Bobby Bland, Dixie Hummingbirds, Shep & The Limelights, Dinah Washington, Muddy Waters, Johnny Otis, and B.B. King. Otis talks with Fairmont Hotel spokesperson John DeMers about the Blue Room in New Orleans and the Fairmont Hotel's Send Us the Suds shampoo giveaway.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Jimmy Reed, Coasters, Jimmie Lunceford, Hank Ballard, Joe Turner, Clovers, Johnny Otis, Otis Redding, Bobby Bland, and LaVern Baker.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live from the Paramount Hotel, New Orleans, 1988-08-29; 1 Audiotape Reel 10 in.; Featured guest(s): John DeMers
      EC10 2358
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h53w82dm1q
      Otis plays the music of The Johnny Otis Show, B.B. King, Richard Berry, Billie Holiday, Swan Silvertones, Hank Ballard & The Midnighters, Dinah Washington, Coasters, Fats Domino, and Lionel Hampton. Otis and DeMers talk and discuss the Fairmont Hotel's Send Us the Suds shampoo giveaway contest. Comedy segment. Otis introduces three female fans.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1988-09-19; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2458; EC10 2459; EC10 2460
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n69m11f18r
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Stevie Wonder, Etta James, Aretha Franklin, Count Basie, John Lee Hooker, Penguins, Pete Rodriguez, Robins, Shirelles, Larry Williams, Dinah Washington, Bobby Bland, Jimmy Witherspoon, Jessie Hill, Saunders King, Sonny Thompson, Coasters, B.B. King, and Ray Charles.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Muddy Waters, Johnny Otis, Delmar Evans, Sonny Boy Williamson, Dixie Hummingbirds, Aretha Franklin, Fats Domino, Louis Jordan, Clyde McPhatter, James Brown, and Roy Milton.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Lightnin' Hopkins, Jimmie Lunceford, Johnny Otis with Charles Williams, Louis Armstrong, Joe Turner, Chuck Berry, Odells, Clarence "Frogman" Henry, Barbara George, Hank Ballard, Dinah Washington with Brook Benton, Staple Singers, Lionel Hampton, and Blind Lemon Jefferson.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Live From the Fairmont Hotel in New Orleans, 1988-10-03; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2461; EC10 2462; EC10 2463
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/841861800x
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Ruth Brown, Joe Jones, Maxine Brown, Sam & Dave, Fats Domino, Ray Sharp, Faye Adams, Ray Charles, Johnny Ace, LaVern Baker, and The Dixie Hummingbirds. Otis tells the story about a mixup in Savannah, GA between Faye Adams and Marie Adams, then talks about Little Miss Cornshucks and LaVern Baker.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of the El Dorados, Jerry Butler, Johnny and Shuggie Otis, Sugar Cane Harris, Carla Thomas, Howlin' Wolf, Professor Longhair, Bobby Bland, Little Willie John, Temptations, Lightnin' Hopkins, Spiders, B.B. King. Otis and guests talk about New Orleans artists.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Jimmie Lunceford with Lionel Hampton Orchestra, Brook Benton, Chubby Checker, Jimmy Reed, Chuck Berry, Otis Redding, Jimmy Liggins, Regents, Mitty Collier, and the Dominos. Otis and friends discuss the importance of older recordings and promote The Johnny Otis band's shows at the historic Blue Room.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1988-10-17; 2 Audiotape Reels 10 in.
      EC10 2464; EC10 2465
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p98851c23f
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Freddie King, Coasters, B.B. King, Little Richard, Louis Jordan, Lionel Hampton, Little Esther, Supremes, Johnny Ace, Little Willie John, Chords, Howlin' Wolf, Cadets, Bobby Bland, Ernie K-Doe, Impressions, Otis Redding, Drifters, Meadowlarks, Soul Stirrers, Louis Armstrong, Muddy Waters, Six Teens, Lowell Fulson, and Bobby Charles.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Jimmy Reed, Ray Charles, Lloyd Price, Solomon Burke, Ike & Tina Turner, Big Joe Turner, Sticks & Brownie McGhee, Billie Holiday, El Dorados, Staple Singers, Barbara George, Professor Longhair, Faye Adams, Aretha Franklin, Z.Z. Hill, Fats Domino, Otis Redding, Frankie Lymon, Silhouettes, and Marvin Gaye.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-01-30; 3 Audiotape Reels 10 in.; Featured guest(s): Bernie Pearl, Harmonica Fats
      EC10 2466; EC10 2468
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c67w62mm2g
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Marvin & Johnny, LaVern Baker, Marvin Gaye, Amos Milburn, Sam Cooke, Bobby Lewis, Johnny Ace, The Monotones, Lee Andrews & The Hearts, Camille Howard, Lloyd Price, and Billie Holiday. Live performance by Pearl and Fats. Otis, Pearl, and Fats talk about working together and marriage; Otis talks about his dogs; Fats talks about where he's from and says hello to his family; Otis, Pearl and Fats talk about favorite harmonica players.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Smokey Robinson & The Miracles, Little Richard, Chuck Berry, Jay McShann & Charlie Parker with Walter Brown, Miriam Makeba, Jimmy Reed, and B.B. King. Live performance by Pearl and Fats. Otis and guests talk about their radio playlists and the blues legends they feature.
      Tape 3: Otis performs live with Pearl and Fats, takes phone calls, and plays the music of Larry Williams, Ray Charles, J. Otis, Percy Mayfield, Count Basie, Ella Fitzgerald & Louis Armstrong, Ben Webster & J. Otis, Lee Dorsey, Richard Berry, John Lee Hooker, Etta James, Duke Ellington, Clovers, Lowell Fulson, and Louis Jordan.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-02-06; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.
      OT 9972; OT 9973; OT 9974; OT 9975; OT 9976; OT 9977
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/880v73j313
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of B.B. King, Lil Green, Little Richard, LaVern Baker, Louis Armstrong and Ella Fitzgerald; Otis and friends chat about next records, play Bo Diddley, and Percy Mayfield.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Jackie Brenston, Memphis Slim, Jay McShann, Ray Charles, Dorothy Love Coates & the Gospel Harmonettes, Billie Holiday, King Curtis, The Ikettes, and discuss Ike Turner.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Sam Cooke and Bobby Parker, takes phone calls, plays Louis Jordan, Lionel Hampton, Moonglows, and Duke Ellington.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Aaron Neville, Faye Adams, Aretha Franklin, Coasters, Bobby Bland, Charles Brown (with Johnny and Shuggie Otis), Count Basie, Johnny Otis Show, T-Bone Walker, and Johnny Otis Orchestra.
      Tape 5: Otis plays "Harlem Nocturne" (end of song); Otis plays the music of Arthur Connelly, Jack Dupree, Ray Sharpe, Guitar Slim, Hank Ballard, Robert Johnson, Stevie Wonder, and Ruth Brown. Promotes food drive for the homeless.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of the Swan Silvertones, Dinah Washington, Jimmy Witherspoon, Little Junior Parker, Katie Webster, Fontella Bass, Barrett Strong, Bessie Smith, Chuck Willis, and Big Maybelle.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-02-13; 7 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Gene "Mighty Flea" Connors, A Cappella All-Stars
      OT 9978; OT 9979; OT 9980; OT 9981; OT 9982; OT 9983; OT 9984
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k81j532r7n
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Jr. Walker & the All-Stars, Lloyd Price, Coasters, Smokey Robinson & the Miracles, Mercy Dee, Johnny Otis feat. Mighty Flea, Aretha Franklin, and Wilson Pickett.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, Wilson Pickett, Bobby Bland, Count Basie feat. Jimmy Rushing, Dorothy Love Coates & the Gospel Harmonettes, and the Drifters. Live performances from the A Cappella All-Stars ("Rockin' Robin" and "I'm So Proud") and Gene "Mighty Flea" Connors.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of the Drifters, Ray Charles, B.B. King, Lowell Fulson, Dinah Washington, Stevie Wonder, and Hank Ballard & the Midnighters. Live performance by the A Cappella All-Stars ("Your Love Keeps Lifting Me Higher" and "This is Dedicated to the One I Love"), Johnny Otis, and Mighty Flea.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Stevie Wonder, Hank Ballard & the Midnighters, Elmore James, Ruth Brown, Etta James. Live performance from Johnny Otis feat. Mighty Flea.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Johnny Otis, Little Milton, Duke Ellington, Jay McShann feat. Walter Brown, Memphis Slim, Louis Armstrong, James Brown, Heartbeats, Jesse Belvin, and Johnny Otis feat. Shuggie Otis.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Jesse Belvin, Johnny Otis feat. Shuggie Otis, Gladys Knight & the Pips, Chuck Berry, Lee Dorsey, Tommy Ridgely, Joe Turner & Pete Johnson, and Bo Diddley. Live performance by the A Cappella All-Stars ("So Fine").
      Tape 7: Otis plays the music of Bo Diddley and promotes his food drive.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: Performers with the Names of U.S. Presidents, 1989-02-20; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Jimmy Tolbert, Samantha Shad, Norm Harris, A Cappella All-Stars
      OT 9985; OT 9986; OT 9987; OT 9988; OT 9989; OT 9990
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b49425rn9t
      Tape 1: Featured artists are those with the names of US presidents; Otis plays the music of Big Joe Turner, Clarence Carter, Jackie Wilson, Ike & Tina Turner, Johnny Adams, Roosevelt Sykes, Muddy Waters, Don Gardener, and Frankie Ford.
      Tape 2: Featured artists are those with the names of US presidents; Otis plays the music of Lester Young, Robert Johnson, Johnny Taylor, Little Johnny Taylor, Wilbert Harrison, and Duke Ellington.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Little Son Jackson, Ray Charles & Betty Carter, Wilson Pickett, and Billie Holiday & Teddy Wilson.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of the Harmonizing Four, Dinah Washington, Jimmy Reed, Johnny Otis feat. Ben Webster, and Aretha Franklin; Otis and Jimmy Tolbert discuss Harlan Leonard's band, the Club Alabam in the 1940s, Bobby Shad, and Ben Webster.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Aretha Franklin, Marv Johnson, LaVern Baker, Norm Harris & the A Cappella All-Stars, Count Basie, and Faye Adams; Live performance from the A Cappella All-Stars ("This Magic Moment" and "My Girl").
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of the Drifters, Joe Turner and Pete Johnson, Lloyd Price, Clarence Henry, the Dubs, Ray Charles, Marvin Gaye & Tammi Terrell, Martha & the Vandellas, and B.B. King.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: KPFK Fundraiser, 1989-02-27; 8 Audiotape Reels 7 in.; Featured guest(s): Bernie Pearl
      OT 9991; OT 9992; OT 9993; OT 9994; OT 9995; OT 9996; OT 9997; OT 9998
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/217q67r22q
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Joe Tex, Etta James, Bobby Bland, Little Richard, Tommy Tucker, King Curtis, and Aretha Franklin.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Louis Jordan and Ray Charles.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Jimmy Reed, Billie Holiday, Gene Chandler, and the Spaniels.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of B.B. King and the Drifters.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Stevie Wonder, Four Tops, Chuck Berry, Count Basie, Coasters, and the Harptones.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Ray Sharpe, Mercy Dee, Hank Ballard & the Midnighters, and the Supremes.
      Tape 7: Otis plays the music of Duke Ellington, Elmore James, Little Richard, and Dinah Washington.
      Tape 8: Otis plays the music of Mickey and Sylvia, Wilson Pickett, Eddie Floyd, Louis Armstrong, Clovers, and Johnny Ace.
    - The Johnny Otis Show: KPFK Fundraiser, 1989-03-06; 8 Audiotape Reels 7 in.
      OT 9999; OT 10000; OT 10001; OT 10002; OT 10003; OT 10004; OT 10005; OT 10006
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/989r07b83t
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Big Joe Turner, B.B. King, Hank Ballard & the Midnighters, Jimmy Reed, Drifters, Fontella Bass, and Ramsey Lewis.
      Tape 2: Fundraising show for KPFK; Otis plays the music of the Coasters, Silhouettes, Roy Milton, Stevie Wonder, and Little Richard.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Koko Taylor, Aretha Franklin, Fats Domino, and Ray Charles.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of the Dixie Hummingbirds, Staple Singers, Four Tops, Temptations, and B.B. King.
      Tape 5: Otis plays the music of Bobby Bland, Sam Cooke, and Johnny Otis Show feat. Shuggie Otis. Otis discusses the history of the song "Open the Door Richard" and censorship of live performances.
      Tape 6: Otis plays the music of Count Basie, Charles Brown, Crows, Dinah Washington, and Little Junior Parker.
      Tape 7: Otis plays the music of Booker T and the MGs, Louis Armstrong, Aretha Franklin, and T-Bone Walker.
      Tape 8: Otis plays the music of the Clovers, Otis Redding, Howlin' Wolf, Muddy Waters, Duke Ellington, and Billie Holiday.
    - The Johnny Otis Show, 1989-03-13; 6 Audiotape Reels 7 in.
      OT 10007; OT 10008; OT 10009; OT 10010; OT 10011; OT 10012
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r171887363
      Tape 1: Otis plays the music of Ray Sharpe, Otis Redding, Aretha Franklin, Staple Singers, T-Bone walker, Little Junior Parker, Coasters, and Marvin Gaye.
      Tape 2: Otis plays the music of Marvin Gaye, Irma Thomas, Andy Kirk, LaVern Baker, El Dorados, Dreamlovers, and Jimmie Lunceford.
      Tape 3: Otis plays the music of Jimmie Lunceford, Bull Moose Jackson, B.B. King, Duke Ellington, Bobby Bland, and Hank Ballard.
      Tape 4: Otis plays the music of Ray Charles, Lee Dorsey, Earl Hines & Billy Eckstine, Curtis Mayfield & the Impressions, Jimmy Reed, Charles Brown, and Stevie Wonder.